Viewers all over the world,
let the power of God come upon you, upon your flesh!
The anointing is in the house!
Right now, it is time to put your demand on the anointing!
Unbelief blocks God's blessing.
Right now, begin to put your demand on the anointing!
Let the power of God come upon you in the name of Jesus!
Anywhere sickness or infirmity is located,
I command that infirmity to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Sickness in your bones, liver, kidneys - whatever name they call it -
never a sickness Jesus cannot cure!
Cancer, HIV - whatever name they call it - never a sickness Jesus cannot cure!
I command them right now, in the name of Jesus, let the power of God come upon you!
Let the power of God come upon you!
Anywhere sickness is located,
anywhere disease is located,
anywhere infirmity is located,
out, in the name of Jesus!
Rejoice!
Let your story change!
The story of your health, career, business, finances - let them change!
Let them change!
I can see Him changing your story!
In Jesus Christ's name, we pray!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers all over the world, this is a new dream - take it!
A new dream - breakthrough!
A new dream - prosperity!
A new dream - good health!
A new dream - reconciliation!
A new dream!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Rejoice!